Martin, Albert, Papers /3051
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Plant Cafeteria, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Plant Open House, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- N.Y. Society Semantics, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Human Element in Accident Prevention, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Employee Manuals + Notes, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Alcoholism in Industry, 1952-1956 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Forbes, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- 12 Noon, April 10th, 1957-1959 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- NCR Safety Course, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Job Analysis, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Fluctuations in Income + Employment Thomas Wilson, 1942-1948 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Income + Employment Theodore Morgan, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Theory of Wages J.R. Hicks (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Business Cycles and National Income Alvin Hansen, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Research in the Social Sciences (Methods), 1939-1960 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Methodology in the Social Sciences Phil. Educ. Gen. Ed. Pri (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Essays in the Theory of Employment Joan Robinson, 1919-1937 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Theory of Wages, 1934-1948 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Background of Social Sciences readings Stewart Brown S. Univ., 1949 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Table of Scheduled Charges: A. For Loss of Member- Traumatic or Surgical, B. Impairment of Function, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Investigation of Accident, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Industrial Safety Consultants Course, Job Safety Analysis, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- American Standard Method of Recording and Measuring Work Injury Experience, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Instructions for Use of Workmen's Compensation Forms, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Clinical Approach to Accident Prevention, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Job Analysis: Case Study, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Supervisor Accident Report (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Formulas for Accident Frequency Rates, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Role Playing: The Case of the Safety Line, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Two Methods of Estimating Accident Costs, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Example of Simonds' Method of Computing Accident Costs, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Job Analysis Schedule, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Job Safety Analysis and On-the-Job Instruction, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- "Management Controls Man Failure Which Causes or Permits" Graphic (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Delman Forge Company, Harvard Business School, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Industrial Organization ad Safety Case Studies, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Safety Inspection Check List (Box 27, Folder 18)
- The Case Of James Montgomery, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Learning Experiment Number Sheet (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Principles for Safe Plant Operation, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Case Study: The Washington Foundry, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Six Point Safety Program, Discovering Causes, Effecting Cures (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Accident Analysis Chart (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Monthly Summary of Injuries (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Accident Report Summary, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Problem of Immortality, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Misc. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Idealism: W.E. Hacking, 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Critique of Judgement (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Ethics of Socialism (Box 28, Folder 5)
- The Problem of Evil (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Notes, 1935-1938 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Ch. History Anec. + Med. (Box 28, Folder 8)
- NotesPapers, Etc. (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Renaissance: Revolt on Authority (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Reformation: Protest of Aroused Conscience (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Notes (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Notes (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Lecture Notes - Thomson 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Rel. Realism: Macintosh Weisman (Box 28, Folder 15)
- A Priori in Rel. Experience, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Psychiatry and Voc. Goals, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Occupations USA (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Recognition of Long Service, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- G.A.W., 1956 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- The Org. Chart, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- No Time Clocks, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1956-1958 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- People, Skills, and Jobs, 1957-1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Facts about the Federal-State Unemployment Insurance Program, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Major BLS Programs, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- The 1959 Steel Negotiations (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Industrial and Labor Relations, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- A Catalogue of Books in Economics, 1910-1956 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Industrial Relations Center, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- A Complete Guide to Modern Library and Vintage Books, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Understanding Macroeconomics', 1965 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Praeger, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Book Week Paperback Issue, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Growing with New York State Electric and Gas (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Labor Problems: Case and Readings, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Salary Rating Plan, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Job Rating Manual, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Endicott Johnson Corporation, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Employee's Handbook, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Handbook for Employees - Jamestown Plant, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Manpower Research Bulletin No. 3, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Course in Function of Mgt., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- A Survey of Management Development, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Changing Times, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- How to Read and Understand Financial and Business News, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Milliken Station, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Economic Dimensions of America's Corporation, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Personnel Training and Equipment (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Lilly at a glance (Box 29, Folder 34)
- United States Department of Labor, 1913-1962 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Bridge to Employment, 1913-1963 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- The Manpower Development and Training Act, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- The National Apprenticeship Program, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Handy Reference Guide to the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Job Horizons for College Women in the 1960's, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Crucible Steel Company of America, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Harper Torchbooks, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Some Recent Wiley History, Political Science and Sociology Texts, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Development and Society The Dynamics of Economic Change (Box 29, Folder 44)
- The Social Sciences, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- California Paperbacks, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- List of Free Materials Available to Professors, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- Hillary House Publisher Ltd., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- The Contemporary Perspectives in Philosophy Series, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 49)
- Foundations of Philosophy Series, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 50)
- Business and Economics, 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 51)
- Cornell Conference Report, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Dun's Review and Modern Industry, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Misc. Newspapers, 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Telling Employees About Business Operations: Profits, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Telling Employees About Business Operations: Profits, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Pullman Incorporated, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Annual Report to Policyholders, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- comparison of Sales Wages, Profits, and Dividends, 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Automatic Voting Machine Corporation, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- 1952 Progress Report Esso Standard Oil Company (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Background for Tomorrow - Thompson Products, Inc., 1901-1951 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- 'Talking it Over' - National Association of Manufacturers, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Mutual Telephone company - Sixty-Ninth Annual Report, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Automatic Voting Machine Corporation Annual Report 1955 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- How to Tell Your Business Story in Your Annual Report, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Company Annual Reports to Employees, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Annual Report - Marlin-Rockwell Corporation, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Esso Highlights - Esso Standard Oil company, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- 'Your Metropolitan Services' - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Changing Times - The Kiplinger Magazine, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- The Erickson Agency's Magazine, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Effective Employee and Community Relations, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Developing a Better Understanding of Business - Effective Employee and Community Relations, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- The Royal Bank of Canada Monthly Letter, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Selig Perlman, 1937-1953 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Notes, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Dunlop (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Perlman, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Philosophy of Labor Movement, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Tanenbaum, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Report Haxie, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Web of Pull Theory, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- The Econ Impact of Unions (Box 30, Folder 33)
- White Collar Unionism (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Sydney + Beatrice Webb (Box 30, Folder 35)
- J.R. Commons (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Marxism + Unions, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Misc., 1951-1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Misc., 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Retirement, 1954-1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Preparing Employees for Retirement, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Doing Something for the Disabled, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Something can be done about Chronic Illness, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Company Practices Regarding Older Workers and Retirement, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- The Psychological Corporation Test catalog, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- The Lectures of Dr. Lillian M. Gilbreth, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Steelways, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Factory Management and Maintenance, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Productivity, 1955-1964 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Labor + Industry, 1955-1962 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- The Incident Process, 1960-1965 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Employment, 1955-1962 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Agreements - U.S.W.A., I.A.M., 1954-1960 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- 'Box 41', 1955-1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- 'Box 42', 1955-1966 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- 'Box 43', 1955-1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Federal Reserve Bank 1963-1965 Monthly Reports (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Cases in Business Administration Volume 5, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Intercollegiate Bibliography - Selected Cases, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Labor Problems, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Labor Arbitration (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Junior College Journal, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1914-1964 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- 'Box 45', 1958 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Conference Board Reports - Tuition-Aid Plans for Employees, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Industry and Education, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- The University of Chicago The Home-Study Department, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- NYSSILR Summer Session 1954 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Study Courses, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- The University of Buffalo Bulletin, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- A Home-Study Department Announcements 1954-55, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Morse Chain Company -and- Craft Lodge No. 520, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Getting Ahead in Industry, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Industrial Relations Research At Universities, 1952-1953 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Disability Benefits - Questions and Answers about Disability Benefits to Employees (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Freedom vs. Communism, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- The Journal of Social Issues, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Glass - One of Man's Oldest Materials enters a New Era of Usefulness in our Everyday Living, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Making the Year Count, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Employing Older Workers, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- 'Box 46', 1955-1959 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Detroit's Senior Citizens (Box 34, Folder 19)
- 'Box 47', 1955-1962 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Guaranteed Wage and Supplementary Unemployment Pay Plans (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Union Security and Checkoff Provisions (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Union Security and Checkoff Provision, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- 'Box 50', 1955-1959 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Job Description and Classification Manual, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Labor Laws and Agencies, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- NLRB Policy on the Employer's Duty to Supply Economic Data for Bargaining, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- News Clippings, 1955-1960 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Collective Bargaining, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Company Health Programs for Executives, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Company Group Insurance Plans, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Cooperative Medical Programs, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Cooperative Medical Programs, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Box 49, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Company Medical and Health Plans, 1954-1960 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Collective Bargaining Provisions, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Union Decisions in Collective Bargaining, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Box 52, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Contents of 399 Employee Magazines, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Employee Publications, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Information Bulletins for Supervisors and Executives, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Employee Magazines and Newspapers, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Service for Employee Publications, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Synchroscope, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- This is Gardner, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- The National Cash Register Company Adding Machine Division, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- The National Cash Register Company Adding Machine Division, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Your Retirement Benefits (Box 36, Folder 13)
- International Salt Company, Inc. - District 50, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- International Salt Company, Inc. - District 50, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Collective Bargaining, 1943-1948 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Esso Research and Engineering Company, Bayway Plant -and- Independent Laboratory Employees, 1946-1955 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Automatic Voting Machine, 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- The Evolution of Managerial Ideas in Industrial Relations, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Collective Bargaining, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Esso Research and Engineering Company, Bayway and Linden, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Box 54, 1956-1960 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Economic Development Africa (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Economic Development China, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Economic Development The Common Market Countries, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Economic Development U.S.S.R., 1962 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Economic Development Japan, 1959-1962 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Economic Development Theory + Dome Applications, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Economic Development U.S.A. (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Economic Development Latin America, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Collective Bargaining, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- The AFL in the 1920's A Strategy of Defense, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- The Outlook in Industrial Relations, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Progress In Labor-Management Relations, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Labor Education Outside The Unions, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Box 56, 1955-1962 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Box 57, 1954-1964 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Retirement Systems, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Health Costs of the Aged, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Act - as Amended, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Box 58, 1956-1965 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- 1965 Annual Paperbound Book Guide for Colleges (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Business and Economics, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Irwin Books in Economics and Business, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Harper Torchbooks, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Retirement Primer, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- 123, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Three Economics Texts From St. Martin's (Box 38, Folder 7)
- New York Stock Exchange Fact Book, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- The Social Sciences, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Scholarly Books in America, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- A Jigsaw Puzzle with Fifty-Eight Pieces, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Census Publications - Statistics of Agriculture, Business, Governments, Housing, Manufactures, Minerals, Population, and Maps, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Crowell Sociology Texts, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Houghton Mifflin Company (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Philosophical Library, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- The Foundations of Modern Economics Series, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- History college Texts (Box 38, Folder 17)
- AMA Management Bookshelf, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Crowell Political Science Texts, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Box 60, 1955-1965 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Box 61, 1956-1965 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- The Impact of Arbitration on Industrial Discipline, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Arbitration Discharge: Cases (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Notes (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Begin Now to Enjoy Tomorrow, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- My Time is my Time (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Box 62, 1955-1965 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Esso Preparation for Retirement, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Esso Preparation for Retirement, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 28)